One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
The Sake I Brewed to Drink With You
Ce saké que j'ai fabriqué pour toi
The island is flying?!
L’île flotte dans le ciel…
Can this... truly be happening?!
Je crois rêver ! Comment est-ce possible ?
Just how powerful is Kaido?!
Les pouvoirs de Kaido sont-ils donc sans limites ?
Why?!
Why ?
How come?!
Qu’est-ce que tu fiches ici ?
Marco the Phoenix?!
Marco le Phénix !
Marco the Phoenix Former Whitebeard Pirate
Marco, Le Phénix Ancien membre des pirates de Barbe Blanche
Well then, let's try this!
Bon, bah y a qu’une chose à faire.
Chopper!
Chopper !
Hot! Hot! I'm burning!
C’est chaud ! Je prends feu !
Hey! That's going too far!
Faut se calmer sur l’incendie !
I thought we were on the same side!
Moi qui te prenais pour un allié !
Marco!
Marco !
They sure are testy...
Ce que vous êtes impatients.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
Ouille, ouille, ouille !
Chopper! I'll put it out!
Je vais t’éteindre, Chopper.
It's burning my arm!
Ma main brûle !
It'll scorch me too–
J’ai pris feu !
Or not?
Ou pas ?
This flame...
Étranges flammes…
Ouch! Ouch! Ow, ow...
Calme-toi, Chopper.
It's really hot–
Je suis en feu !
Or not?
Ou pas…
I'm on fire but I'm not getting burned!
Je flambe sans brûler… J’ai ni chaud ni froid…
This flame is comfortably...
Ces flammes font du bien, elles sont…
warm...
à peine tièdes.
– Dr. Chopper!
– Dr Chopper !
We're ready to produce the antibodies!
Nous allons bientôt produire le remède, venez vite.
Miyagi, Mink Doctor
Miyagi, Mink Médecin Tristan, Mink Infirmière
It's a swarm of ice ogres!
Une meute de démons de glace !
Miyagi! Tristan! Get out of here!
Miyagi ! Tristan ! Prenez vos jambes à votre cou !
Gotta warm them up one way or another!
Je vous chope tous.
Phoenix Pyreapple!
Don du phénix !
The chill in my body is fading!
Je ne sens plus mon corps frissonner…
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Ouille, ouille !
Wh-What was I...?!
Je revis…
Omasa!
Omasa !
Thank goodness! You came to your senses!
Tu es revenu à toi, quelle bonne nouvelle !
Omasa...!
Omasa !
Well, it's like you were saying. It's sapping your body heat.
Je génère de la chaleur, comme t’as demandé.
Once your stamina runs out, you'll turn back into an ogre!
Si je me fatigue trop, ils se changeront de nouveau en démons.
I only bought you a bit of time!
Je t’ai juste gagné du temps.
You're a lifesaver!
Tu me sauves la vie.
Time's just what the doctor ordered!
C'est exactement ce dont j'avais besoin !
Miyagi! Tristan!
Miyagi ! Tristan !
Are you two okay?!
Vous vous en êtes sortis ?
Y-Yes!
Sans trop de mal…
We're fine!
Je vais bien.
Let's hurry and get to work!
Vite, lançons la production.
We'll give you the support you need!
On va vous filer un coup de main.
Thank you! I can focus if I'm in that tower!
Merci bien.
Marco!
Marco…
He and that damn tanuki really know how to chap my ass!
Cette petite enflure et le raton laveur prennent un peu trop leurs aises.
Hey, you bums! Catch that tanuki already!
Trouvez-moi le raton laveur, bande de nazes !
Why would he bother saving your lousy asses?!
Vous ne croyez quand même pas qu’il va vous sauver ?
But... that tanuki...
Mais, il a l’air sincère…
Keep your eyes on the prize!
Vous avez pas à hésiter !
If you don't wanna bite the dust, crush that tanuki and take back the antibody!
Si vous voulez pas crever, allez le liquider.
I see... I think I've got the gist of the situation.
D’accord…
Hey, Roronoa!
Hé oh, Roronoa !
Weren't you on your way to slice 'n dice Kaido?
Tu voulais pas aller découper Kaido ?
If you wanna get to the rooftop...
Si tu te rends au sommet,
I'll give you a lift!
je peux t’y déposer.
You guys are too good to be dealing with these chumps!
T’as un peu mieux à faire que te farcir les sous-fifres, non ?
But Chopper needs our support...!
Il faut qu’on assiste Chopper, tout de même…
Don't worry... Sir Skeleton!
Nul besoin. Sac d’os !
We'll hold the line for Sir Tanuki!
Nous défendrons le raton laveur, j’en fais le serment.
Thanks, you guys! I'm counting on you!
Merci, chef !
Hold it, you son of a bitch!
Pas si vite, sale enfoiré...
Apoo!
Apoo !
Give me back the antibody...!
Tu vas me rendre l’anticorps !
If I lose it...
Si je me le fais piquer…
my ass is freakin' grass!
ma vie est fichue, vous comprenez !
Give it a rest!
Qu’il est lourd !
He won't stay down!
Celui-là, il est redoutable.
I don't mind taking on one more job!
Finissons-en avec lui.
Sir Tanuki, hurry into the tower!
Rentre dans la tour, raton laveur.
– Apoo!
Apoo !
X Drake Formerly of the Soaring Six Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit: Allosaurus
X Drake Ancien Tobi Roppo Fruit du Dinosaure, version Allosaurus
This guy...
Celui-là…
Drake?!
Drake !
So he really has switched sides!
Il s’est vraiment retourné contre nous.
Roronoa Zoro. If you would consider me an ally...
Roronoa Zoro, si tu me penses dans ton camp…
then I'll hold them here while you go ahead!
Fonce sans regarder ce qui se passe ici.
At least you know how to bet on the winning horse!
Au moins, tu as le don de parier sur le bon cheval.
4th Floor Inside the Castle
3e étage À l'intérieur du Château
Sanji! Sanji!
Sanji ! Sanji !
Perhaps Sanji sensed a powerful foe and went to hold them back on the third floor!
Il a sûrement senti un redoutable adversaire au deuxième,
Maybe...!
Tu crois ?
Guess my observation haki isn't that good yet.
Va falloir que je bosse mon Haki de l'Observation.
I'm not picking up Sanji's presence at all!
J’arrive pas à le localiser ou à sentir sa présence.
Do you feel something, Jinbe?!
Tu ressens quelque chose, Jinbe ?
Yeah...
Oui.
There are quite a few enemies in here...
Beaucoup trop à mon goût.
And...
Et surtout…
they're quite strong!
un redoutable opposant.
Seems like one of us should remain on this floor!
Je pense qu’il vaut mieux que je reste seul ici.
I'll create an opening. You go on ahead!
Je vais faire diversion. Continue sans moi !
Let's do this!
Je vais me lâcher un peu.
General...
General...
Launcher!
Launcher !
Right-Brain Tower Inside the Dome
Tour du cerveau droit À l'intérieur du Dôme
Time to raise a little hell!
Et pour finir de mettre le souk…
General...
General...
Cannon!
Cannon !
Get back, men!
Écartez-vous, les gars !
Who the hell fires something so haphazardly?!
Tu sais faire autre chose que tirer partout ?
You're asking for it!
Tu t’y crois un peu trop, mon gars !
I dig the look, bro!
Tu vois que t’as une belle gueule…
A triceratops!
le tricératops.
Sasaki Soaring Six Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit: Triceratops
Sasaki Tobi Roppo Fruit du Dinosaure, version Tricératops
So you're a dinosaur!
Monsieur est un dino !
Just give up! This is the strongest creature that ever lived!
Résigne-toi, les dinosaures sont les plus puissants êtres vivants.
You'll be nothing but scrap when I'm done with you!
Je vais te réduire en pièces détachées !
There's no scratching the sheen of Wapometal!
Comme si tu pouvais briser l’incassable métal Wapo !
Outside the Onigashima Dome
À l'extérieur du Dôme d'Onigashima
It's the Soaring Six!
C’est les Tobi Roppo !
Ulti Soaring Six Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit: Pachycephalosaurus
Ulti Tobi Roppo Fruit du Dinosaure, version Pachycéphalosaurus Page One Tobi Roppo Fruit du Dinosaure version Spinosaurus
Where did they go?!
Où ils sont passés ?
I am ever so vexed!
Ils m’ont diantrement énervée…
I shall crack her detestable head wide open! That bitch!
J’ai très envie de leur démolir le crâne.
He ran off that way!
Il est parti par là.
Banquet Hall 3rd Floor Inside the Castle
Salle de banquet 2e étage À l'intérieur du Château
Banquet Hall 3rd Floor Inside the Castle
Salle de banquet 2e étage À l'intérieur du Château
Banquet Hall 3rd Floor Inside the Castle
Salle de banquet 2e étage À l'intérieur du Château
Banquet Hall 3rd Floor Inside the Castle
Salle de banquet 2e étage À l'intérieur du Château
Slow down, silly!
– Reviens ici ! – Reste donc ici !
Damn! What is this?!
Qu’est-ce que c’est que ça ?
Let me out!
Dénouez-moi ça !
You can stop struggling now...
C’est qu’il se débat, le coquinou…
Be a good boy... Don't try to run.
Hors de question que tu t’enfuies, mon petit chéri.
After all...
Beau jeune homme…
didn't you say that you loved me?
Il y a un petit instant, tu m’as proclamé ton amour…
Black Maria Soaring Six Ancient Spider-Spider Fruit: Rosamygale Grauvogeli
Black Maria Tobi Roppo Fruit de l'Araignée, version Rosamygale grauvogeli
Black Maria Soaring Six Ancient Spider-Spider Fruit: Rosamygale Grauvogeli
Black Maria Tobi Roppo Fruit de l'Araignée, version Rosamygale grauvogeli
Black Maria Soaring Six Ancient Spider-Spider Fruit: Rosamygale Grauvogeli
Black Maria Tobi Roppo Fruit de l'Araignée, version Rosamygale grauvogeli
Black Maria Soaring Six Ancient Spider-Spider Fruit: Rosamygale Grauvogeli
Black Maria Tobi Roppo Fruit de l'Araignée, version Rosamygale grauvogeli
Black Maria Soaring Six Ancient Spider-Spider Fruit: Rosamygale Grauvogeli
Black Maria Tobi Roppo Fruit de l'Araignée, version Rosamygale grauvogeli
Black Maria Soaring Six Ancient Spider-Spider Fruit: Rosamygale Grauvogeli
Black Maria Tobi Roppo Fruit de l'Araignée, version Rosamygale grauvogeli
Stay by my side forever. I'll make you my pet.
Fais-moi le plaisir de rester ici. Je subviendrai à tous tes besoins.
Don't be ridiculous! I...
T’es dérangée !
But...
Par contre…
everywhere...
Où que je regarde…
I look...
À gauche comme à droite…
it's women, women, women...!
Il y a des femmes à perte de vue !
Is this...
Cet endroit…
heaven?
C’est le paradis ?
He's clearly lost it.
Il a un grain, lui.
You're absolutely precious...
Comme tu es mignon…
Big Cat Cafe 4th Floor
Cafélin 3e étage
So Straw Hat went on ahead...
Le Chapeau de paille s’est tiré en premier.
This'll be a real headache for ol' Kaido...
Il va nous ennuyer Kaido, ce sale énergumène.
Would you kindly stop...
Ce serait sympa…
picking on my men?
que tu lâches la grappe de mes hommes.
Who's-Who Soaring Six Ancient Cat-Cat Fruit: Saber-Toothed Tiger
Who's Who Tobi Roppo Fruit du Félin, Version Tigre à Dents de Sabre
Who's-Who Soaring Six Ancient Cat-Cat Fruit: Saber-Toothed Tiger
Who's Who Tobi Roppo Fruit du Félin, Version Tigre à Dents de Sabre
Who's-Who Soaring Six Ancient Cat-Cat Fruit: Saber-Toothed Tiger
Who's Who Tobi Roppo Fruit du Félin, Version Tigre à Dents de Sabre
Who's-Who Soaring Six Ancient Cat-Cat Fruit: Saber-Toothed Tiger
Who's Who Tobi Roppo Fruit du Félin, Version Tigre à Dents de Sabre
Who's-Who Soaring Six Ancient Cat-Cat Fruit: Saber-Toothed Tiger
Who's Who Tobi Roppo Fruit du Félin, Version Tigre à Dents de Sabre
Who's-Who Soaring Six Ancient Cat-Cat Fruit: Saber-Toothed Tiger
Who's Who Tobi Roppo Fruit du Félin, Version Tigre à Dents de Sabre
Who's-Who Soaring Six Ancient Cat-Cat Fruit: Saber-Toothed Tiger
Who's Who Tobi Roppo Fruit du Félin, Version Tigre à Dents de Sabre
Who's-Who Soaring Six Ancient Cat-Cat Fruit: Saber-Toothed Tiger
Who's Who Tobi Roppo Fruit du Félin, Version Tigre à Dents de Sabre
Who's-Who Soaring Six Ancient Cat-Cat Fruit: Saber-Toothed Tiger
Who's Who Tobi Roppo Fruit du Félin, Version Tigre à Dents de Sabre
Who's-Who Soaring Six Ancient Cat-Cat Fruit: Saber-Toothed Tiger
Who's Who Tobi Roppo Fruit du Félin, Version Tigre à Dents de Sabre
Who's-Who Soaring Six Ancient Cat-Cat Fruit: Saber-Toothed Tiger
Who's Who Tobi Roppo Fruit du Félin, Version Tigre à Dents de Sabre
Who's-Who Soaring Six Ancient Cat-Cat Fruit: Saber-Toothed Tiger
Who's Who Tobi Roppo Fruit du Félin, Version Tigre à Dents de Sabre
Former Warlord Jinbe, Knight of the Sea, acting with all the decorum of a child?
Jinbe le paladin des mers, je te trouve bien superficiel
I am the helmsman of the Straw Hats!
Je suis le timonier de l’équipage au chapeau de paille.
Would you do me the honor of using this worthier title?
C’est plus valorisant, merci de t’y tenir.
Oh, my bad.
Mince alors, tu m’en vois navré.
I caught a glimpse of you back in your Warlord days...
C’est que je t’avais déjà vu, quand t’étais un Grand Corsaire.
What?!
Pardon ?
Well, it's no big deal.
M’enfin, passons là-dessus.
Who are you?
Qui es-tu ?
Man, who could I possibly be?
Va savoir, hein.
Perhaps removing your mask will jog my memory.
J’en aurai le cœur net…
I'd love to see you try.
Je te la montrerai pas.
Forbidden Storehouse Inside the Dome
Réserve À l'intérieur du Dôme
We can hide here for a bit since this room has long gone unnoticed.
Ici, personne ne nous trouvera.
What am I seeing?
Sais-tu ce dont il s’agit ?
A statue of a dragon.
Une statue de dragon.
It once stood at the entry point of the island, but it was placed in here after my friend broke it.
Elle était à l’entrée de l’île, avant.
Your friend?
Ton ami ?
Yes...
Oui.
A few years ago...
Il y a des années…
he came to kill my father!
cet homme est venu tuer mon père.
What gives? This place is deserted...
C’est dingue, y a pas un chat.
Intruders!
Alerte, des intrus !
If you're not Kaido, get lost!
Y a que Kaido qui m’intéresse !
Ace!
Ace !
Guys, go save the children while you can!
Foncez libérer les enfants !
Got it!
C’est compris.
Leave it to us!
On revient !
This one won't stay down!
T’es une coriace, toi !
Who are you?! Tell me your name!
Dis-moi qui tu es ! Donne-moi ton nom !
Right back at you!
Commence par le tien !
I'm Ace!
Je m’appelle Ace.
I'm here to take Kaido's head!
Je viens prendre la tête de Kaido.
I found them! Over here!
Je les ai trouvés, venez là !
Don't be scared. We're getting all of you out of here.
Restez calmes. On vient vous sauver.
Yeah, but we need to hurry.
Vite, tout le monde dehors.
You're pretty tough.
C’est que t’es forte, toi.
Ace!
Ace !
All the children are okay!
Les enfants sont sains et saufs.
But we can't find Kaido anywhere!
Par contre, pas une trace de Kaido !
What?!
Pardon ?
My father went on an expedition!
Mon père et ses lieutenants sont en expédition ailleurs.
not a single officer is here!
Vous ne trouverez personne ici !
Your father?!
Ton père ?
So she's Kaido's daughter?!
Mais alors… c’est elle, la fille de Kaido ?
I'm Yamato!
Je m’appelle Yamato.
I think it's about time you stopped tearing up the place!
Vous vous êtes assez excités, vous croyez pas ?
If you have time to wonder who I am,
Si vous vous ennuyez au point de poser ces questions,
I'll take you up on that.
Avec grand plaisir.
But is it wise to let us go?
Tu es sûre de nous laisser partir ?
It's not like I'm under any obligation to protect this island.
Rien ne m’oblige à défendre l’île.
Alright, let's get back to Wano.
Dans ce cas, cap sur le pays de Wano.
Your families are waiting for you.
Vos parents vous attendent.
Truly, we can't thank you enough!
– Merci ! – Nous n’oublierons jamais votre bonté !
You sure, Ace?
T'es sûr de rester ici, Ace ?
That means going back to the mainland without you.
De notre côté, on va rentrer sur l'île.
That's right. Keep them safe. I'll catch up later.
Ouais, occupez-vous des petits. Je vous rattraperai plus tard.
I'm not convinced someone as strong as you isn't at least one of their captains...
Qu’une femme si forte soit pas capitaine, ça me fait tiquer.
Let's settle this!
Réglons-ça !
I was bored anyway.
Ça tombe bien, je m’ennuyais.
Let's fight!
Viens te battre !
Fire Fist!
Poing ardent !
What's the story? Shouldn't someone as strong as you be out at sea?!
Je comprends pas.
It's all his fault...
Tout est sa faute.
Kaido's fault!
C’est à cause de Kaido !
Of all the people to have as a father...
Ça me débecte qu’il soit mon père.
It's all your father's fault?
Tout est la faute de ton père, c’est bien ça ?
That's your excuse?
Tu te cherches des excuses ?
You can't...
On choisit pas ses parents, Yamato !
Shut up! Don't you think I know that?!
La ferme ! Je suis au courant, pas besoin de la ramener.
Do you really?
Je crois que tu comprends pas.
Physical shackles are one thing, but if you hate your father this much...
Si tu peux pas le voir en peinture…
why shackle your heart as well?!
brise les chaînes affectives qui t’y enchaînent.
Yamato!
Yamato !
What do you want to do?!
Qu’est-ce que tu veux, au fond de toi ?
I admit...
Tu as raison.
I was holding myself back.
Je me suis enchaîné seul.
But now I realize...
Je viens d'ouvrir les yeux.
I wanna set out to sea and go on adventures!
Moi aussi, je veux prendre le large et partir à l’aventure !
I wanna live freely like Oden!
Je veux vivre libre, comme Oden avant moi !
Set out to sea...
Voguer en mer…
To sea...
Explorer les océans…
I wanna leave this damn island...!
Quitter cette fichu île…
I wanna live freely!
Je veux vivre une vie de liberté !
That's the spirit, Yamato!
C’est ça, Yamato !
It's good to want those things!
Voilà ce qu’il faut te dire.
Now you know what to do.
Alors, délivré de tes doutes ?
Yeah!
Oui !
And he came home in tatters!
Et là, il est rentré amoché comme pas deux !
When we were kids, he got us into all kinds of trouble!
Il me donnait du boulot quand on était gamins, je te le dis.
Your little brother sure is something!
C’est un marrant, ton frangin !
Right?!
T'as vu ?
So tell me, what's it like out there?!
Comment ça se passe, hors de ce pays ?
Are there a lot of young up-and-comers?!
Y a plein de nouveaux pirates, non ?
Young...? Let me think...
Des jeunes pirates ? Ouais.
Everyone's talking about Caven-something.
Cavenmachin-truc fait parler de lui.
Yeah?!
Ah oui ?
Well, I'm in a class of my own,
Moi, je suis un peu à part,
but I heard some dangerous guys are running wild in every sea.
mais de sacrés personnages font les quatre cents coups loin d’ici.
Mm-hm! Mm-hm!
Raconte, raconte !
There's Kid in the south...
Il y a Kid au sud,
Law in the north and Bege in the west.
Law au nord, Bege à l’ouest.
But the toughest one of all will set sail in a few years...
Mais le plus coriace ne partira que dans quelques années.
My kid brother!
Mon petit frère, bien sûr !
He'll blow 'em all outta the water!
Il va devenir très important.
You sure do like to talk about your brother.
T’as pas bientôt fini de me bassiner avec lui ?
So what?! You should listen!
Râle pas, t’as juste à m’écouter.
You... That hurts!
– Ça fait mal ! – Lâche-moi, toi.
The truth is I'm the one who broke this dragon statue first.
En vérité, cette statue…
But he said...
Et là, il m’a dit…
"Let this be a warning to Kaido that I'll be back!"
que ça servirait d’avertissement à Kaido
I see...
Je vois...
I was unaware that a pirate once tried to save Wano...
Il y avait donc un pirate qui voulait libérer notre pays.
It pissed off my father,
Mon père s’est fâché,
but in the end, he never met Ace.
mais il a jamais croisé la route d’Ace.
Wait...
– Comment ? – Ton père ?
Wha– Hey, don't be so scared!
Pas besoin d’avoir peur, oh !
Hey, but I really do hate him!
Je ne peux pas le voir en peinture. Je suis Oden, je vous dis !
That is even more confusing!
Je n’y comprends plus rien !
I'm not scary! I hate Kaido!
Il ne faut pas avoir peur de moi. Je déteste Kaido.
I longed for the sea and adventure, so I became Oden, who lived freely!
J’ai pris le nom d’Oden par amour pour les océans et l’aventure.
We understand for the most part.
Merci de votre sollicitude.
Thank you for tending to us!
Vos soins nous obligent.
Stop being so formal and get over here!
Revenez ici et parlez normalement !
But Yamato,
Cela dit, Yamato,
where is this would-be savior of Wano now?
où est ce fameux homme qui voulait sauver mon pays ?
Ace...
Ace ? Mort il y a deux ans.
Otama, you knew Ace?!
Tu connais Ace, Otama ?
Yes, he was like a brother to me!
Oui ! C’était un bon ami à moi.
I decided to believe in Ace and try to become a kunoichi,
J’ai tout fait pour devenir kunoïchi parce que je croyais à son retour.
but Big Bro Luffy was mean and said to me...
Luffy m’a annoncé la nouvelle sans le moindre tact.
Ace is dead.
Ace est mort.
He said it to me out of the blue.
Apprendre ça aussi brusquement, ça m’a fait pleurer.
Oh, sorry about that.
Je suis désolée. Il est comme ça, y a rien à faire.
But y'know, Otama, it was really hard for Luffy, too.
Mais tu sais, Otama, Luffy aussi a beaucoup souffert.
Back when it happened...
Le jour de sa mort...
He's ruining it!
Tu commences à me gonfler…
Listen up, folks!
Arrêtez-moi Marco, bande de soûlards !
Don't let him run free!
Empêchez-le de faire son petit numéro !
C'mon, he saved us...
Alors qu’il nous a sauvés ?
But if we don't do what His Awesomeness wants, he'll kill us anyway...
C’est ça ou se faire tuer par Queen…
Don't just stand there!
C’est pas le moment d’hésiter, obéissez aux ordres !
I won't be facing Kaido directly at this point.
À ce stade, ce sera pas moi qui vais m’en prendre à Kaido…
Nico Robin! Skeleton Man! You've got places to be!
Nico Robin ! Le sac d’os ! Vous avez un boulot à faire.
Get to the castle!
Foncez au château !
Now's our chance.
Partons.
If you insist!
C’est si gentiment demandé.
Go to hell, Marco!
Tu vas crever, Marco !
You're finished, Marco the Phoenix!
T’es un homme mort, Marco le Phénix !
You ready?
Prêt à partir ?
Do it!
Oui !
Damn that Marco!
Marco, espèce d’enfoiré !
Nice going!
Pas mal.
You're pretty relaxed for someone about to face down an Emperor!
Je te trouve bien tranquille, tu vas te mesurer à un Empereur.
Why should I be scared of Kaido?
Ça changera quoi que je flippe ?
If my captain gives the order, I follow it.
Mon capitaine veut se le faire, alors on va se le faire.
Look at me, rooting for Straw Hat– No...
J’attends beaucoup du Chapeau de paille.
I wonder how he would've felt hearing his brother picked a fight with an Emperor, too...
S’il apprenait que son frère cherche des noises à un Empereur
I'm begging you, Pops!
Je t’en prie, Père !
I said no, you little shit!
Non, pauvre idiot.
Ace, I've told you plenty of times now...
Je t’ai déjà expliqué les choses mille fois, Ace.
who the 2nd Division commander was before you...
Qui commandait la deuxième flotte dont tu as hérité ?
and why the position was vacant for so long.
Pourquoi j’ai gardé le poste vacant ?
Wano practices a policy of isolation, so information never comes out.
Le pays de Wano reste isolé, aucune information n’en sort.
We were unaware that Lord Oden had died until several years after the fact.
Nous n’avons appris la mort du seigneur Oden
We toyed with the idea of raiding Wano, but to what end?
On a pensé à lancer un assaut,
Can you imagine the toll it would take?
Tu imagines les sacrifices ?
The toll?
Quels sacrifices ?
Then, let me go by myself!
Laisse-moi au moins y aller seul.
I made a promise...
Je l’ai promis à quelqu’un.
Kozuki Oden couldn't take that guy down...
Battre un homme que Kozuki Oden a échoué à vaincre ?
Meaning you couldn't beat him on your best day!
Dans tes rêves !
Don't overestimate yourself, Ace!
Reviens sur terre, Ace !
Y'know, Oden's strength was the real deal!
Oden, il était vraiment fort.
You really wanna take down the big shots, Commander Ace!
T’aimerais te faire un gros poisson, hein, commandant Ace ?
Give it a rest, Teach!
Boucle-la, Teach.
Ace isn't motivated by hunting "big shots."
C’est pas ce qui intéresse Ace.
Dammit...
Bon sang…
I need to get stronger so I can fulfill my promise...
Si je deviens pas plus fort, je pourrai pas tenir ma promesse.
That's what you're shouldering, huh?
C’est ça, ce que tu cherches ?
Ace, if Pops ever gives the go-ahead, do not forget to extend an invitation my way.
Ace, si Père nous autorise à partir,
Count me in, too.
Pareil, pense à moi.
In that case, we can probably kick his ass now...
On pourrait déjà gagner, quoi.
How are you still overestimating the situation...?
Faut vraiment que tu apprennes à évaluer des forces…
Marco!
Marco…
Don't think we'd just let you through!
Va pas croire que tu passeras si facilement.
Superstar Queen Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit: Brachiosaurus
Queen - Superstar Fruit du Dinosaure, Version Brachiosaure
Besides, all the samurai up top are dead by now!
Les samouraïs dehors sont sûrement tous déjà morts.
And when Kozuki Oden's son is dead, the battle will be over!
Une fois le fils d’Oden éliminé, la guerre sera terminée.
Superstar King Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit: Pteranodon
King - Superstar Fruit du Dinosaure, Version Ptéranodon
Wano shall be reborn as the pirate empire of New Onigashima!
Wano deviendra
If that's what you believe, then you really have a screw loose!
Vous êtes trop optimistes, si vous y croyez vraiment !
Stop squawking, little bird!
Ferme-la, piaf de malheur !
Damn! Is he invincible?!
Il est invincible ma parole... C’est quoi, ce pouvoir de malade ?
You're up against the force of a new era now!
C’est tout le nouvel âge que vous vous mettez à dos !
The Beast Pirates will crush this "new era," along with everything else!
Le nouvel âge, comme le reste,
Wha–
Quoi ?
Now, now... Just let him pass!
Soyez gentils, laissez-le passer.
And up you go!
Gare à l’atterrissage !
You seriously just threw me?!
T’aurais pu prévenir !
B...
Lu…
Big Bro Luffy is Ace's little bro?!
Mon frérot Luffy est le petit frère d’Ace ?
That's right.
Bah oui, tu savais pas ?
Because when I mentioned Ace, he said so casually...
Quand je lui ai parlé d’Ace, il m’a répondu si froidement…
Ace is dead.
Ace est mort.
I said some mean things to Big Bro...
J’ai été vraiment méchante avec lui.
He would've been mean right back if it had bothered him.
S’il en avait quelque chose à faire, il te l’aurait dit.
Don't worry!
Ne t'inquiète pas.
But...
Quand même…
Big Bro... I'm sorry!
Frérot… Je suis tellement désolée !
Like I said, don't worry.
Puisque je te dis que c’est rien.
Anyway, let's give this "Otama Strategy" of yours a shot!
Allez ! On va mettre à exécution le plan dont tu parlais.
Forbidden Storehouse Inside the Dome
Réserve À l'intérieur du Dôme
This person you speak of was Roger's son,
Cet homme est le fils de Roger et le frère aîné de Luffy ?
Is that true?!
C'est vrai ?
Mm-hm.
Oui.
You all brought Luffy to Wano, right?
C’est vous qui avez amené Luffy au pays de Wano, c’est ça ?
That is correct...
Tout à fait.
There are as many pirates as there are stars in the sky, but they're the ones you met...
Que vous l’ayez rencontré lui parmi une myriade de pirates
and you brought them to this country...
et que vous l’ayez amené ici…
I can't imagine this as anything but fate!
pour moi, c’est le destin !
Because...
Après tout…
Luffy's name bears the initial D!
Le nom de Luffy comporte le « D. » !
Yummy!
Que c'est bon !
Fire really hits the spot!
Les flammes, y a que ça de vrai.
Delicious!
Miam !
I'm so stuffed now!
J’ai le nuage plein...
I'm fully recharged!
Je suis chargé à bloc !
Did you finish your meals?
Vous avez fini de manger ?
Yes, Mama!
Oui, Mama.
I'm good to go!
Je suis plein.
Okay then, let's go!
Parfait, on repart.
Straw Hat isn't here yet?
Le Chapeau de paille n’est pas encore là ?
Hey, Kaido!
Hé oh, Kaido.
You can kill as many as you want as long as you leave Nico Robin alive.
Tue qui tu veux si ça te chante, mais épargnes Nico Robin.
Don't you have a member of the three-eye people who can read the ancient script?
Ta fille de la tribu des trois yeux sait pas lire les caractères anciens ?
Oh, Pudding?
Qui, Pudding ? Qui sait…
I can't wait for her true awakening anymore.
Je ne peux plus attendre l’éveil de son troisième œil.
Yeah, that make sense...
Ah, si tu le dis…
5th Floor Inside the Castle
4e étage À l'intérieur du Château
This is about all we can do to assist, so please, go on ahead!
C’est tout ce nous pouvons faire… Avance au fond.
These are the stairs to the rooftop!
L’escalier te mènera au toit.
Thanks, Shishimamushi!
Merci, Sicimamushi.
It's Shishilian.
Moi, c’est Sicilion.
Yeah, I'll never forget it...
Je l’oublierai jamais, les gars,
The way you guys defended Raizo with your lives!
que vous avez protégé Raizo au péril de votre vie.
Thank you!
Merci !
Later!
Je file.
So where are you planning on dropping this island?
Et donc, où tu feras tomber l’île ?
There is a castle in the Flower Capital that symbolizes the Kozuki.
Il y a un château qui symbolise les Kozuki à la Capitale des Fleurs.
I heard they're having a festival.
En plein festival ? Il y aura beaucoup de victimes.
Who cares?
Je m’en fiche. Des esclaves, c'est pas bien compliqué à trouver.
It'll be a glorious capital.
Ça deviendra une belle capitale.
And the lode poneglyph?
Et ton Road Ponéglyphe, il est là-bas ?
Your true colors are already showing!
Tu pourrais cacher un peu ce qui t’intéresse.
Don't give me that!
À d’autres !
You're like a little brother to me!
Je te vois toujours comme un petit frère.
On that day when Rocks was defeated at God Valley,
Sur God Valley, le jour où Rocks a été anéanti,
I gave you the Mythical Fish-Fish Fruit.
c’est moi qui t’ai donné ton Fruit du Poisson de type Zoan mythique.
You're indebted to me for life, Kaido!
T’as une dette à vie envers moi, Kaido.
Whatever!
Ouais, c’est ça…
Let's go get it, then we'll talk!
On en reparlera quand il sera entre nos mains…
Let's get the One Piece!
Le One Piece !